Presented by cinema service
executive producer kang woo-suk
cha seung-won
jang seo-hee
directed by kim sang-jin
ghost house
take a look around the house . I 'm sure you 'll love it .
You couldn 't even dream about
finding a house like this in this city .
Even jesus christ himself couldn 't build a better house .
The previous residents rushed
out of korea unexpectedly ...
shortly after they moved in .
Look , there 's no need to paint or wallpaper .
All you got to do is move in .
It 's fantastic , isn 't it ?
It 's got the best quality interior , see ?
Can you believe it , a house with such
a beautiful ocean view for so cheap !
If you let this chance go by , you 'll definitely regret it .
Deal ?
Dad ...
dad !
Dad ... !
What ?
Why do we have to move all the time ?
Why don 't you buy a house , then we wouldn 't have to move so much !
Pil-gi , get up , it 's dinnertime !
Pil-gi !
Pil-gi
pil-gi , what 's wrong ? Get up !
Get your hands off , let me go , you jerk !
The briquette fumes in your house almost killed my son !
Are you refusing to pay the hospital bill !
You think it 's not fair ?
- Dad , calm down ! - Then sue me !
My back is breaking , ass !
We 're almost there , this hill is killing me !
Dad , you got to stop fighting !
However poor we are , we have to keep our dignity .
I 'm sick of transferring schools all the time !
I hate this shit !
How ungrateful you are ! Can 't you see , your dad 's doing his best !
Push !
Are you trying to be cheap about the water ?
You telling me that we can only wash twice a week ?
- Pil-gi gonna win ! - No way !
Good boy .
Never lose a fight against the son of a homeowner .
Let them throw us out ! We can always find another place to live .
Pil-gi 's such a pussy !
Hey , man !
Fuck off , we 're moving !
Dad , hang on ! You 'll be okay !
Hurry , he needs a doctor !
Dad !
Doctor !
Pil-gi !
Dad , the doctor 's on his way .
You have to buy a house of your own some day .
Yes , dad .
It 's all i ask of you , live in your own house !
Oh , dad , don 't die ! Don 't leave me behind !
Residence of park pil-gi
dad ... !
I bought a house !
Dad ... this is my house !
Oh , dad !
Finally , your dream 's come true !
My house !
Hello .
- Hey , pil-gi . - Can you hear me ?
I can hear you fine .
Oh damn , the reception here is really bad .
You must be tired , take it easy , honey .
I 'm fine !
Come and have a look over the weekend .
So you finally bought a house , and you know i don 't like working .
Can i finally quit my job ?
No way ! You know we both need to work .
Both of us earning is best .
Leave the picture hanging to me , all right ?
I hung one , already .
Hello . Hel ... !
Hello !
Damn .
What the ... !
What ?
How the hell did this fall ?
Man , on the first day !
Why won 't this nail go in ?
This is really annoying !
No , this is my house . I got to suck it up !
Shit , i got to piss !
What the ... ?
Did i scare you ?
Yeah , you did .
- This place is great ! - Isn 't it ?
Look at the view ! It couldn 't be better !
- You like it ? - Yeah !
Soo - kyung , this is the happiest moment of my life !
Hello , you called for a driver , right ? I 'm in front of the bar .
Yes , we can leave right away .
Sir , we 're almost there . Give me the detailed address .
Let 's have some more beer !
We 've had enough . Let 's go home .
You don 't know when to stop !
You should have some control .
Hey , mister , where 's the man who was just run over ...
he 's gone , see .
You bastard . Drink by yourself from now on .
You son of a bitch !
This isn 't a crosswalk . Shouldn 't jaywalk ! Be more careful !
This job is killing me !
Stop complaining and do your job .
Just forget this ever happened , that 's all .
- It makes your life easier , right ? - What do you mean ?
Don 't be a bad drunk !
I couldn 't be a better drunk !
Well , hello , what a finely built young man !
I haven 't seen you around . Are you new here ?
Yeah , sorry , i should 've said hello earlier .
Oh , you probably moved into the apartments up on the hill , right ?
No , i live in the house behind the complex .
That 's right . I bought it .
Have you found ... anything strange about it ?
What do you mean ?
What are saying ? The house is haunted ?
Which is the reason why it sold for so little , right ?
Yeah , that 's right .
Listen , i 'm not in a mode for jokes .
So cut the ghost shit out ! You 're not making any sense ?
Then what , i 'm a ghost too , is that right ?
Calm down , i 'm just warning you to take care of yourself .
How the hell does this fall off the shelf ?
Only weak-minded people
see illusions of ghosts !
Do i look weak to you or what ?
No , you look very manly .
Let me show you something .
Don 't worry about a thing , even if there is a ghost .
You know what ? I was a marine !
And marines can handle anything , even ghosts !
How much !
35,000 won , honey .
What ?
35,000 won .
Hey , what kind of market do you think you 're running ?
The sign outside says 'super market ' right ?
The basic idea of super markets is to give discounts !
A 10 % discount for all customers .
So , it 's 31,500 , not 35,000 right ?
Man , i should 've wrung out the wet rags !
Hey !
You don 't know when to shut the fuck up !
Get off of me , please !
- Just sing . - What ?
I said , sing !
What do you mean sing !
If you don 't , i 'll beat the hell out of you .
Do you know how embarrassing it is !
Sing , or i 'll break you neck !
- Any requests ? - Anything .
Those damn punks are driving me crazy !
Oh , i may be young to you ~
but do not say i 'm too young , babe ~
oh , my mommy .
Pil-gi ...
leave this house now !
If you leave now , you can still live .
Leave , if you wanna live .
If not , i 'll kill with my bare hands !
Die !
Do you want to die !
With my bare hands !
Get the hell out .
Die !
Stop , no !
Leave , this is my house !
Please don 't do this to me !
If you wanna live , get out .
Officer , help me ! My house is haunted .
I saw a ghost .
I saw a ghost in my house !
What 're you talking about ? Come in .
Where the hell did you see the ghost ?
- Wait , i 'm scared ! - Stop being a baby !
I swear , it threw a knife at me .
I got no idea .
Hey the only thing i see is your underwear .
Come in and take a look .
Come on , hurry up !
So you got drunk and had a fight , right ?
No way ! I haven 't had a drop to drink .
So why the hell is your house such a mess ?
I told you , the ghost did it !
Are you playing us for idiots ? Come and show me .
The couch started dancing and it attacked me !
And the knife ... !
Oh my , this is crazy .
Then look , turn the tv on !
The guy on tv turned into a ghost ...
and crawled out of it like this !
Are you taking police officers for pushovers ?
No , but just 5 minutes ago ...
you have any idea what we police go through !
We look for the missing kids ,
and get all kinds of crazy calls .
On top of all that ,
we get drunken idiots taking leaks at the station .
We 're fucking busy handling all this shit !
And now we got to deal with ghosts crawling out of tvs and throwing knives ?
Listen , i 'm not sure who threw the knife but ...
i got no idea how that actor crawled out of the tv !
I don 't give a shit !
- Let 's go . - Yes , sir .
Wait , officer !
What 's wrong ? You look awful !
What are you doing here ? This isn 't your section .
- I came by to let you know . - Know what ?
The new foreman 's a tough one .
In fact , he 's a legend .
He 's been working in the field
for 30 years since he was 17 .
He was working overseas
for the last 6 years and has come back .
Pil-gi , come here .
Yes , sir .
Let me introduce you to the new foreman .
You bastard , we 've met before right ?
I guess it was fate that brought us together , huh .
I 'm jang kil - bog .
I know what i 'm doing . Leave everything to me .
Wait a minute .
I don 't know what you 've done in the past , but over here , rules are rules .
Our team strictly follows the q / c plan .
The q / c ? How long did it take you to develop it ?
Five months , why ?
Five months ?
Well , for me , being a 30-year veteran ,
my eyes and instincts are all it takes .
Eyes and instincts ? Then what use is the q / c plan ?
Look kid , the world isn 't always what it seems to be .
Hey , are you all right ? What happened ?
Nothing happened ?
Keep your damn nose out of my ghost house !
Don 't misunderstand , i 'm just worried about you .
You don 't need to worry a thing !
I told you . Only weak-minded fools see ghosts .
Want me to show you how tough i am again ?
No , no , that 's alright .
There 's no such thing as ghosts on earth . How much ?
Let me see ...
with the discount ! 10 % !
You give me such a hard time .
What 's with that shelf ?
Congratulations , you 're the first one
of us marine friends to buy a house !
What 's with the mess ?
Been a little busy , you know .
Anyways everything 's set for your wedding !
You 're all staying the night , right ?
So eat and drink as much as you want !
Hey , looks like you 're scared of sleeping alone .
Get out of here !
No , i can 't stay over .
I gotta go home in a few hours .
Oh no , you 're leaving so soon ?
Change your plan , and be with us , right ?
Hey , i 'm starving . Give me something to eat .
Sit , sit .
- Stop messing around ! - Your feet stink !
Cheers !
Hey , where 're the chicks at around here ?
Hey shut up ! I gotta answer the phone !
Keep it down !
Hello , honey .
- Drinking again ? - No way ! I 'm still at work !
Get your ass home , now ! You forgot your promise already ?
- Are you insane , jerk ? - Sorry , honey .
Move your ass now , or you 're dead tonight .
- I 'm coming , hon . See you , honey . - Right now !
Sorry , but i gotta run .
Why ? Stay over . All of you !
I 'd like to , but my kid 's sick and ...
i guess we 'll go too .
Give us a ride .
But the rest of you are staying right ?
I told you i can 't .
It 's too late already .
What the ... !
You promised you 'd stay .
Let 's go .
I 'm not letting you go !
No , you can 't leave .
We 're sorry , pil-gi ,
but you know we can 't help it tonight .
What 's with you anyway ?
I want you to stay with me tonight .
There 's something going on , isn 't there ?
The truth is that ...
this house is ...
haunted !
What ?
This house is haunted .
I 'm not kidding .
- That 's bullshit ! - Let 's go .
Do you expect us to believe that shit ?
- I 've seen it ! - Are you crazy or something ?
- Hey , what 're you doing in the car ? - Let me go with you .
What 're doing ? Get out .
You get in the back .
Hey , it 's your house right ! Forget about the damn ghost .
Let 's go .
Get him out !
What 's wrong with you man ?
Get out , come on !
You 're a disgrace to the marines !
Remember , " marines can kill ghosts too . "
Thanks for the dinner ,
call me if the ghost gives you any trouble !
I wanna go with you
don 't ever come back here again !
Poor boy , i saw this coming !
The ghost came back again !
Again !
Hello !
- What ? - Give me my money back .
- Get off of me ! - Give me my money !
Have you lost your mind ?
You knew it all along and conned me into buying that haunted house !
No one forced you to buy it .
- Quit your crying ! - What ?
You liked it and you bought it , you moron .
And now you 're saying it 's my responsibility ?
You asshole !
If you 're thinking about selling it , doing this shit never helps , right ?
Still you wanna hit me ? Go ahead , stupid ass .
- That house on the hill is haunted ... - hey lady !
There 's nothing to see here . Mind your own business
you wanna hit me , go ahead !
So you want me to help you sell it ?
Forget it , i won 't sell it !
... and of the holy spirit . Amen .
I am heartily sorry for having offended thee ,
i firmly resolve to sin no more .
Oh , lord ! Please expel satan ,
all evil spirits , and whatever !
Dve ' me bhikkhave dhamma
saddhammassa sammosaya
antaradhanaya samvattanti .
Katame dve . Dunnkikkhittam ca
pada-byancanam attho ca dunnito
dve ' me bhikkhave dhamma
saddhammassa sammosaya antaradhanaya
hey , mister !
You 've had enough to drink .
My life sucks . I can 't help it .
I worked day and night to make money ...
to buy this damn house ...
but i can 't even sleep there !
This jacket , i don 't know how long i 've been wearing it .
I can 't even go home
to change clothes .
Then why don 't you go buy some ?
That 's not what i mean , no one understands me .
I 'm lost .
Hey , give me some more soup .
Long time no see !
What a surprise ! Look who it is !
You didn 't bring your friend ?
That jerk had other plans , so i 'm here to have a drink with you .
No one believes me . The snake came crawling of his mouth .
You don 't know how to say hello .
What are you talking about anyway ?
- You 've met before ? - He 's one of my men .
Captain . Mr. Jang .
What 's going on ?
He 's the last person i 'd expect to get this way .
You can 't imagine how terrible things are right now !
So , have you realized
that you can 't do everything by the book or with principles ?
But at the same time , alcohol isn 't the answer , either , boy .
You don 't have a clue ...
about the pain and agony in my heart !
You don 't have a heart !
Don 't have a heart ?
Never mind , let 's just drink .
Man , if you couldn 't handle it , you should 've stopped drinking .
You know you 're killing this old dog .
Damn !
Wow , this kid 's got a beautiful house .
I don 't know your story , but try and get along with him , huh ?
It is possible for a ghost and a person to do it .
No ! Not here !
No ? What am i talking about ?
I didn 't do anything wrong !
Come out !
You wanna win this house ?
Then let 's have a fair fight , huh ?
All right , you wanna throw knives . Try it again !
Come out .
Pil-gi !
Yeah , dad .
Because you got a 100 on your math exam , i 'm gonna make you chicken .
Steamed chicken ? All right .
This chicken 's gonna be good .
Take it easy . Let me check if the water 's boiling .
Oh , dad !
What happened , doctor !
It 's miracle he 's alive . He got struck by lightening twice !
But he doesn 't even recognize me !
He will , some day . Just be patient .
How long will it take ?
We 're doing our best looking
with long-term therapy , so ...
just think positive , it 's the best thing to do .
- Are you all right ? - Oh , my god
it must really hurt .
Soo-kyung .
Do you recognize me now ?
I 'll sell the house .
What ?
Sell the house !
I 'm happy you 're back to your old self !
- Have you seen a ghost before ? - I have !
- What does it look like ? - Like this !
Hey !
You little brats !
A beautiful ( but haunted ) House for sale .
Take a look , sir .
Thank you .
Look at the sea view . It 's priceless !
I really love it .
You 're lucky . This kind of house isn 't up for sale all the time .
And , look at this top quality interior .
It 's beautiful . I love it !
You 're absolutely right . Actually , i wouldn 't be selling ,
except something 's come up
may i ask why ?
I 'm going to be transferred to australia for 3 years .
Take a look at the kitchen .
Nice .
Your right , there 's a balcony .
Transfer ? What bullshit !
I don 't believe he 's such a damn bold liar !
What ? Are you with them ?
Anyway , i love this house !
You said ' love ' ?
But you 're trying to scam these people , aren 't you ?
What are you talking about ?
Can you see me ?
Of course , i 'm not blind miss .
You must have heard some bad rumors ,
but believe me , they 're not true .
Excuse me sir !
Can we take a look upstairs ?
Of course ,
the 2nd floor has a better ocean view .
Thank you .
Shall we ... ?
Look at the two boats floating on the sea .
It 's picturesque , isn 't it ?
It 's goes beyond words .
Come and take a look . I 'm at a loss of words to describe it .
Our kids will love it .
It 's really the best choice for your whole family .
And you can also grow
organic vegetables in the yard .
What a great idea ! Organic food is healthy .
That 's right .
But one thing i 'm concerned
about is whether it 's too windy .
There 's nothing to worry about !
This house survived the last hurricane fine !
Take a look at how strong this house stands .
In the summer we won 't need air conditioning because of the breeze .
- That 's right , it 's really cool . - I can tell .
It would 've been good if the kids could see it too .
It 's so refreshing !
It 's a ghost ...
wait for me ...
- don 't leave me behind . - Hurry , let 's get out of here .
You 're ... still here ?
You should get out , now .
It 's because ... i 'm starting to lose it !
Okay , i admit it , i lied .
This house is horrible .
So please , get out of here .
I apologize alright .
So stop staring at me like that .
You have to get out now .
You can see ... me ?
I told you , it 's dangerous to be here !
This can 't be happening .
You can see me , for real ?
This is not a good time to be kidding around .
So hurry , let 's get out of here !
I 'm telling you . You 'll get hurt if you stay in this house .
I can 't help you .
Fine , it 's your life , do what you want .
She won 't listen to anybody !
What ... you ?
What are you , twins ?
I don 't understand how you can see me .
My answer . I see you with my eyes .
Now , are you satisfied ? Get out !
What 's going on ? Are you the ... ?
You can 't be seeing me .
You can 't be hearing me .
This isn 't happening . I can 't belive it !
Who the hell are you ?
I 'm the owner of the house .
What ? Do you wanna die ?
You can 't believe what you see , right ?
I used to be the same .
I told you , the world isn 't what it seems .
I see a ghost ... a real ghost .
You see that guy , going up the stairs .
He died , in an accident , 8 years ago ...
but he 's been working , non-stop ever since .
I was injured in the same accident , but ...
i survived amazingly in a month .
And i 've been able to see ghosts ever since then , whether i like it or not .
Just like you do now .
In time , you 'll get used to seeing them .
There 's nothing you can do about it .
The truth is that humans are the scary ones .
Ghosts are actually friendly .
This is my house , get out of here .
You must be kidding . This is my house !
I 'm telling you , leave !
No , it 's not me . It 's you that has to move out !
So you 're staring at me , so what ?
Don 't get the wrong idea . You think i 'm scared of you ?
Why don 't you transform yourself into something else ?
Cause i 'm really not afraid of you !
Come out .
Don 't be chicken , come out and get me !
Where the hell are you hiding ?
Come on out , ghost or whatever you are !
You scared of me or what ? Did you run out of tricks , huh ?
Let 's go head to head .
All right , let 's put an end to this today . Either you die or i die !
What 's with this guy ? Is he crazy ?
You wanna play games with me ? Come out !
I know you 're here !
Let 's finish it ! Come out , now !
How come he 's isn 't afraid !
I 'm gonna get you , ass !
You think you 're scary ? What a joke !
Next time you 're gonna have to do a whole lot better , got it ?
Wanna try strangling me again ?
I 'd rather watch a scaring movie than see you !
I 'm gonna teach you a lesson !
A lesson about what ?
What 's it this time ? Man , you 're really something !
You did this to the couch the other night , remember ?
What a hopeless girl you are ! All right already !
If doing this make you happy , go ahead .
I can 't believe this !
Who 's at the door ?
Don 't ask me !
What are you filming horror movie or something ?
What 's with the costume ?
It 's too bad . All that effort for nothing !
Who is it ?
Answer me !
You , park pil-gi !
How come you haven 't called me for a week ?
Well ... i was just ...
are you hiding something .
No way ! You know me .
Your girl is pissed off !
- I 'm on vacation starting today . - Oh , you are ?
Hon , soo-kyung , wait !
Oh , she 's turned on so easily !
Please have her keep her shirts on !
You 're lucky !
Look at her ass ! She 's dying to have sex .
Never mind me , just have fun !
Oh , please , no ...
i saw you two doing it the other day .
You 're a crack at it !
I 'm soaking in sweat , pull the covers off .
- No , if you do i 'll ... - all right , goddamn .
Soo-kyung , no more , please .
I told you , stop !
Forget it then . I 'm going home .
Hey , i am sorry , soo-kyung .
Sorry , don 't get the wrong idea .
It 's not what you 're thinking .
Open the door , honey .
Don 't take it the wrong way .
This is killing me !
Open the door . Let 's talk about it , okay ?
Soo-kyung , honey ...
i 'm really sorry .
Calm down .
You 're so pretty ! Oh , my angel !
What 's this ?
Oh , i get it .
Since when have you seen me wearing red panties ?
So you 've been with some other bitch in this house !
No , it 's all a misunderstanding .
You 've cheated on me , damn !
Listen to me !
- It 's not how it looks ! - Then what is it ?
Just calm down !
You said you loved me ,
and so how do you explain this shit !
Wait , please listen to me .
This is so irritating !
Damn !
I can 't believe this .
You bastard , we 're finished .
Soo-kyung !
I 'll kill you ...
yon-wha !
Yon-wha ? That 's the bitch 's name , damn !
- She 's an lg . - An lg ?
What 's that ?
There 're 2 kinds of ghosts ...
one is an lg , meaning 'lingering ghost ' ...
who can 't leave the place that they lived before for some reason .
And the 2nd one is an fg , meaning ' floating ghost ' .
And the one in your house is an lg .
Are you serious ?
All right then , tell me how to deal with this lg , fg or whatever .
First you have to listen to her story
about what makes her linger around the house .
And then ?
You weren 't able to win the fight against the ghost , so ...
now it 's time to negotiate .
Whether human beings or ghosts , communication is key .
None of you can imagine how i feel !
You don 't know how i feel ...
i didn 't do anything .
Hello , please sit .
How cruel !
He needs to learn a lesson anyway .
Why are you so late ?
Well , today is kim 's memorial day .
So we had a meeting at his house .
Have you drunk a lot already ?
We just started .
Hey , let me pour you one .
Today it 's on this boy , so feel free to have as much as you want .
Hey , i didn 't say that . We 're splitting it .
You didn 't really help anyway .
" Need a conversation " ?
An idiot could 've said that !
Okay , i 'm gonna give it a try .
But what do we talk about ?
What the ... !
Are you a bat or something ?
It 's embarrassing to see you doing this crap !
You 're blushing !
I bet , you must 've been practicing all day to surprise me !
Not really .
Listen , give it rest and let 's talk it out .
I don 't want to .
Can you call this 'ghost 's self respect ' ?
Come down , already .
So tell me , what is it that you want me to do ?
That 's simple . Get out of my house .
You 're definitely confused . It 's my house .
You wanna see the contact ?
Or , if you go to the registration office ,
you 'll see that the owner 's park pil-gi .
- This is my house , period . - Is it ?
Then convince me that it is !
I don 't need to .
Just stuff you face pig .
What ? Watch your mouth .
You don 't have any idea how to show respect ?
You started it , jerk .
Jerk ? You 're really pushing my buttons . I 'll kill you !
You think i 'm scared ? What an idiot , i 'm already dead !
Crazy ghost !
The negotiation 's finished ! That 's it !
I 'm not making any concessions !
I 've never heard of such a lousy ghost !
Stop eating ! I paid for this !
She 's not worth giving a try .
What 's her story ?
She just kept saying " this is my house " .
And she 's sharp with cursing and swearing .
She must 've lived a terrible life !
- And she 's even worse than you ! - What the f ... !
All you do is talk about patience and communication .
Sir , this isn 't exactly in accordance with the designs .
Take it easy , it 's perfect .
What the ... !
She must want revenge or something , right ?
Whatever , i don 't give a shit . I 'm not scared any more .
Then find a way for you to live together .
Ghosts are friendlier than humans , in a way .
It 's not time for joking .
Rumors are going around that my house is haunted .
A tv station even called me to cover the story .
Nothing happened ? No ghosts ?
That 's unbelievable ! You look good .
Hey , kid , slow down on the sweets .
Who 're you talking to ?
You have a younger sister who died , right .
Yeah !
- She 's sitting right there . - Where ?
What 's your name ? Sook-ja ? Sook-ja , right ?
Right !
She 's sitting there feasting on chocolates .
Hey , sweets can spoil your teeth , so slow down , okay .
Oh my dear sister .
You got a habit of spying on girls taking baths ?
Who me ? What are you talking about ?
I 'm no pervert !
My husband will come home any day now , so ...
it makes me sick .
Even a ghost changes dresses ? So funny !
This really pisses me off .
You take a bath almost every day .
Think about the water bill i pay .
You don 't ever pay a cent of that .
You just idle away time having fun .
And you don 't even consider the living costs !
Don 't you have any moral ethics ?
What 's the use of taking a bath
if you 're a goddamn ghost ?
According to the project number 60385 's plan , we should ...
hello , this is park pil-gi . That 's right ...
you wanna buy the house ?
Sure , and you 've already seen it ?
Then why don 't we do the paper work tomorrow ?
Don 't worry
a thing about how much over the market price it is .
It would 've been so much better
if you all moved out of these shacks earlier .
Fuck , i 'm fed up with this worthless shits .
Just sign the contract , now !
I don 't have time forever ! Hurry up dammit !
Hey .
You gotta stop popping up out of nowhere like this .
What are you doing ? What 's this ?
Give me that .
Do i have to report every single thing i do to you ?
None of your damn business . I 'm just ...
just what ?
I 'm ...
i 'm moving out .
So you should pack up your things , if you got any .
They 're going to build something here .
- What did you say ? - I 'm moving out .
And they 're going to demolish this house ?
Well ... they 're going to get rid of the house and build a hotel .
It 'll be nice .
You can wait for your husband in a brand new hotel .
No !
I 'm sorry . I understand .
No way !
He was my first and only true love in the 28 years of my life .
And this house was our dream . It was everything .
Congratulation on your wedding !
Sorry for such a small wedding .
What 're you talking about ? I couldn 't be happier .
I 'd be so happy living in a house like this .
- You mean it ? - Of course .
This is ... our house .
I was going to tell you once it was finished , but ...
lunch break , come and eat .
- It 's great . - Hurry up .
I 'm starving .
I love this house .
When the house is finished , let 's take a trip .
A trip ?
It 's been three years and we still haven 't gone on a real honeymoon , so ...
really ? But you know i don 't mind .
- All right , never mind then . - No , let 's go !
What luck , a typhoon hitting during our honeymoon . I 'm so sorry !
It 's fine . I like sound of rain , and besides you 're with me .
Let 's eat .
- Well , we have a house now and so ... - so ... ?
I want to have a baby .
Thanks , honey .
What 's going on ?
Hey , driver !
What 's happening ?
Hurry , give me the stretcher .
Hurry !
Hurry up , we 're losing her !
Mister , can you help me find my husband ?
Oh , please ...
gi-tae !
Hurry , move .
If this house is gone ... ?
Please don 't let this gone , what happens to my husband ?
I 'm begging you .
You can sell it , but this house has to be here .
I sincerely sympathize with you , but there 's nothing i can do .
Don 't cry .
And how can you be so sure you 're husband will come ?
If he were alive , he 'd have come earlier .
If he were dead , he 'd have come as a ghost like you .
I 'm sure that he 's coming dead or alive .
So don 't sell it to this company .
What should i do ?
Only if i could see him ... just once !
Then i 'd be happy and move on .
You 've got to be kidding . You said yes over the phone !
You want more for it , is that it ? I 'll pay 10 million more .
It 's got nothing to do with the price . I just changed my mind , that 's all .
Sorry , but try to find somewhere else .
I 'll be going .
Well , we 've got a problem .
We 've already made a contract with the hotel owner .
Rude son of a bitch !
Park gi-tae ...
no ?
He 's not on the obituaries ,
so he couldn 't have been on the bus .
He was on the bus i bet , and how could he have not come , if he 's alive !
Please have a look at it again .
Does that mean you know one of the survivors who were on the bus ?
Well , yes and no ...
is it possible this record is wrong ?
Well to be honest , i would say yes .
In cases like this , victims are taken to er 's all over the place ,
and sometimes information can get mixed up .
And i wasn 't in charge of it , so ...
what should i do ?
Come this way .
You little brat !
Come down from there , come on .
Hurry up , and come down .
I didn 't do it , i swear .
It 's mean to play tricks on people .
Did you see the mess you caused at the police station ?
I don 't know what happened to you , but this isn 't right .
You might be having fun , but it causes people a lot of trouble .
You belong to the ghost world and you can 't interfere here .
Yes , sir .
Don 't do it again . Promise ?
Good boy , now go home .
- Good - bye . - See you , kid .
I asked all the ghosts around , but ...
no one knows where he is .
He 's not listed on the obituaries .
He could be hanging around the accident site ,
waiting for his wife ?
The accident site ?
Some ghosts
just hang around the place where they died .
He could be waiting for his wife to show up .
Park gi-tae , if you 're here , come out . I wanna see you .
I 'm looking for gi-tae , yon-wha 's husband .
Park gi-tae .
What 's he doing here ? Is he looking for any of us ?
Hello , guys !
You can see us ? Are you a shaman ?
No , not really .
But i 'm here to find a ghost .
Park gi-tae ... wasn 't he the one sitting behind me ?
I haven 't seen him for 2 years .
No , that ghost went after a girl who was here for a picnic .
Is it that guy who was sleeping in the back seat ?
Was it him ?
No , he was sitting with a lady , his wife .
Then could it be the couple sitting in the middle ?
I remember we had to wait ,
'cause the man came back late from the rest area .
No , i was sitting in the middle , and i didn 't see any couple .
How do you know ?
Yu were changing seats all the time ,
looking for the most comfortable one . How selfish !
Selfish ? Me ?
Calm down .
I was reading a newspaper .
Hello ... what ?
Hold on .
Hey , keep it down .
I told you , i won 't sell the house .
No negotiations , period .
Are you threatening me ?
It 's my house , and i won 't sell it ! So what ?
Don 't think you can threaten me , shit !
Mind your own business !
Line up just like the night of the accident !
- Sir ... i am af ... - shut up .
What if the ghost is here ?
Don 't worry a thing .
Even a ghost wouldn 't dare attack me .
Hurry up , moron .
Over there .
Hurry up . Make sure to hit the kitchen too .
What are you doing ? No !
Did you hear that ?
Hear what ? Stop standing there and finish the job .
No !
Get the hell out of here .
Oh , no !
Get out !
Hurry !
Dad .
i 'm happy you got yourself such a beautiful house , sorry i 'm late .
No , that 's all right .
Dad , i missed you so much .
Don 't worry , this house has a strong frame ,
so all you 'll have to do is remodel .
It 's time to say good-bye .
I wish you and your new family happiness .
And yon-wha , get along with my son , all right ?
Let 's take a look .
It would 've been disastrous if the fire spread to the woods .
I 'm sorry to see your house so damaged .
You should 've sold the house
when you could 've gotten more for it .
See what stupid decisions lead to .
By the way , i know it 's terrible timing ,
but there some bad news .
- Is that right ? - Yeah .
This is to inform you that
this house addressed at 43 jangsungop was not built
in accordance with art . 9
and 12 of the construction regulation .
In accordance with art . 69 of these regulations ,
this house is ordered to be demolished .
One last thing .
It takes effects as of today .
Considering that the fire here today violated the law ...
not to mention that it is haunted , it 's best if this house is demolished .
I don 't give a shit . I 'm going to keep this house no matter what .
You officials are taking bribes , right ?
Watch your mouth .
- Get the hell out of here . - Park pil-gi !
All right , but let me tell you something .
I 've been in this fucking business for 20 years .
Remember , i 'm one of the top 10 bastards
in this country for demolishing houses , right ?
You think you win a war against me ?
If you walk away now , i 'll pay for your moving expenses ,
but otherwise , you 're done for . Got it ?
The deadline is midnight .
You think ... this is going to help ?
It will ! I 'm willing to risk my life protecting this house .
Don 't worry , i 'll make sure nothing happens .
How about ...
giving the house up .
What ?
I don 't want you to get hurt , my husband may not come .
That 's enough .
Just talk with the man who wants this house , and you 'll ...
i 'll what ? I 'll do or get what ?
I 'll never give up this house . It 's my house .
And your house ... too .
Hey , i don 't want you to get hurt . Just walk away .
Cut the bullshit . God dammit !
That jerk 's a real pain in the ass !
Sorry , asshole , you want this house ?
Then come and get it .
Don 't hold back . Just do what you got to do .
- Go ! - Yes , sir .
Tear it down , now !
Crush it .
Tear to pieces .
Come on , man !
The cute girl in red shoes will leave .
Now , let 's move .
One more song , please .
Fuck ! Put the fire out .
Hurry .
Be careful , the house might catch on fire !
Don 't worry i used to be pitcher at school .
So i helped friends
throw firebombs at demonstrations .
You see , just trust me .
What are you doing standing around anyway ?
I 'm helpless out of this house .
The only time i actually need your powers , and you can 't help .
His father dying wish was for him to have his own house .
So this boy worked like hell
to buy a house , and he finally made it .
But , as fate would have it the house is haunted .
And , as it turns out ,
that house was everything to the ghost and her husband ,
but when the house was completed ,
she died and her husband went missing
on the first and only trip they ever took .
And she has been there ...
she yearns to find out what happened to her husband ...
and forever waits there for his return .
But a greedy contractor is determined
to demolish the house any time !
We have two choices , we can stay here and enjoy our songs ...
or rush to aid of those poor kids .
They 're resisting like hell !
In the end , there 's nothing he do . Tear it down !
Yes , sir .
No !
Hey ?
I can 't hold on much longer . Get out !
Let 's go , hurry .
Hurry , it 's getting more dangerous !
- I can 't believe this . - That 's strong concrete .
This can 't be happening .
There 's no way ! Ram it harder .
What 's wrong with this ?
It 's ghosts .
- Something 's going on ! - Evil spirits .
Come down you bastard !
Are you all right ?
There 's nothing to be afraid of .
Just do your job , men .
Pil-gi .
Oh , sir .
I am not too late , am i ?
The house was almost done for !
Just do what you came to do !
All out attack !
Attack .
It 's nothing . Stand your ground .
What took you so long ? We almost lost everything .
Fuck , what are you doing ?
Snap out of it you assholes !
No , this can 't be happening .
Are you all possessed or something ?
You won 't believe what i had to do to get the ghosts support force here .
That bastard !
Don 't lay a finger on it ! This is my house !
- Are you yon-wha ? - Yes ?
I heard someone call your name desperately at the hospital !
What ?
I don 't know if he 's still there , but ...
the man next to my room ,
called out " yon-wha " a lot .
Excuse me , is there a patient park gi-tae registered here ?
Well ... not sure , just a moment .
It works .
Great , it 's walking fine .
We 'll carry this bear with yon-wha in it .
- No , it won 't . - Why not ?
She won 't be able to survive in it long .
A woman 's body would be the best for this .
It was perfect .
Who is it ?
Soo-kyung ?
What 's going on ? Are you okay ?
I was worried to death !
Come on in .
The bastards did this !
Why didn 't you call me ?
My boss jang helped me out so everything was okay .
Isn 't that right ?
I didn 't do much , but he 's really lucky .
What if the jerks come back to get revenge ?
No way !
He was thrown in jail for fraud
and forging official documents !
I feel terrible , look at this !
Nothing 's left . We are going to have to start all over again .
And it 's going to take a lot of money , right ?
Well , what 's done is done , so we 'll just have to save up .
We should have that jerk compensate us for the costs !
What ?
What was that ?
Nothing . What 're you talking about ?
I felt something .
What ? Do you feel a pain in your back or something ?
I know there 's something going on that you 're not telling me about .
I don 't know what you 're talking about .
Pil-gi , just tell her the truth and ask her to help .
Soo-kyung is too strong willed so ...
it won 't work unless she 's willingly supportive .
Hey , you 'd better tell me the truth .
This way .
What ?
Why not ?
Do you have any idea what time it is ? Come back tomorrow .
We can 't come back tomorrow . I need to see him today .
You can 't talk to her like that .
Let 's just come back tomorrow .
It doesn 't seem possible tonight .
You 've waited so long ,
what 's another day ?
I 've waited so long already , i can 't wait any more minute .
I have my reasons , so please make an exception this time .
What 's more , he 's in intensive care , only family can see him .
I sure he doesn 't have any family , so how are you related ?
He 's my husband . I 'm his wife .
Security ? Come to the front desk .
Run .
Where are you going ?
- Let 's go up this way . - What ?
- We have no other choice ! - No , yon-wha .
You know how much i 'm afraid of heights .
Fine , i 'll go by myself .
- Hey , come down ! - Oh my god .
Are you all right ? I can 't believe it !
Are you all right ?
I told you not to do it .
Your body 's that of a 60-year-old man , jang , don 't forget it .
- Pil-gi , you go . - What ?
- Hurry . - No i won 't .
I 'm telling you to go !
- I told you this was a bad idea ! - Grab his hands tight !
It 's him , right ?
Is it him ?
Oh , gi-tae ...
are you all right , sir ?
Honey , at last i 'm here .
So , this is why you couldn 't come home .
Sorry , i 'm so late .
I should 've looked for you earlier .
I 'm gonna get the ... why ?
I couldn 't let go , thinking that you might come back to me some day .
And now , everything 's fine .
Nothing matters anymore , we 're together again .
I wouldn 't be here if it weren 't for my friends .
How can i ever thank you ?
It was our pleasure
please find a good place to rest .
Thank you
i 'll never forget what you 've done for us .
Are you park pil-gi ?
We 're terrified .
This ghost or monster whatever it is , is killing us !
It 's an lg .
An lg ?
It 's one of two kinds of ghosts ,
and lg means ' lingering ghost ' ...
it 's kind of technical ,
i 'll brief you when i get the job done .
Have some cold water .
Wow , it 's really cold .
I 'll tell you what , i 'll finish the job before it warms up .
Whether ghosts or human , having a conversation is most important .
I don 't know what your story is for living in this house .
But let 's have a talk , man to man , man to woman , or whatever .
No , help me , not the chicken again !